真不敢相信你会这么说
I can't believe you would actually say that.
我宁可当花生先生 也不当盐先生
I would much rather be Mr. Peanut than Mr. Salty.
不会吧 盐先生是个水手哦
No way. Mr. Salty is a sailor, all right?
他一定是最强悍的零食
He's gotta be, like, the toughest snack there is.
难说 不要惹到玉米坚果
I don't know. You don't wanna mess with corn nuts.
他们是疯子
They're crazy.
我的天 我的天 你们快过来看
Oh my God. Oh my God. You guys, you gotta come see this.
那边有个变态拿着一个望远镜
There's some creep out there with a telescope.
真不敢相信 他居然在看我们
I can't believe it. He's looking right at us.
真是有病
Oh, that is so sick.
我感觉被侵犯了
I feel violated.
感觉很不好
And not in a good way.
怎么有人会这么做
How can people do that?
你们看 丑陋裸男买了一双倒立鞋
Oh, you guys, look. Ugly Naked Guy got gravity boots.
【海盗美剧 友情制作】
-== http://www.hdmeiju.com ==-
新浪微博：@海盗美剧
《老友记》蓝光版 第01季 第20集
风流牙医 The One With the Evil Orthodontist
调校制作：寒 枫
字幕编辑：小龟快快跑
我告诉你们 多年后
I'm telling you, years from now
学生们都会把这个
school children will study it
当作史上最棒的第一次约会来学习
as one of the greatest first dates of all time.
顺利到不可思议
It was unbelievable.
我们非常的自在
We could totally be ourselves.
不需要耍心机
We didn't have to play any games.
你打电话给她了吗
So have you called her yet?
让她知道我喜欢她 你疯了吗
Let her know I like her? What are you, insane?
你们      男生真差劲
Guys!         It's gross.
才过一天而已 你要我看起来很饥渴吗
It's the next day. How needy do I wanna seem?
我说的对 对吧
I'm right. Right?
吊她胃口      没错
Let her dangle.        Yeah, definitely.
真不敢相信我爸妈一直强迫我
I can't believe my parents are actually pressuring me
要我找你们这种人
to find one of you people.
拜托 只管去做
God! Come on. Just do it.
打给她 别摆出一付臭男人的样子
Call her. Stop being so testosteroney.
那是旧金山的特产
Which, by the way, is the real San Francisco treat.
是机器      她的答录机
I got her machine.         Her answering machine?
不是 是她的扫叶机接的
No, interestingly enough, her leaf blower picked up.
那你怎么不说话
So, why didn't you say anything?
不 不 不 不 上次我毫无准备就留言
Oh, no no no no. Last time I left a spontaneous message.
结果讲出"木有温题"这种蠢话
I ended up using the phrase "Yes. indeedio."
你们看 是瑞秋和巴瑞
Look, it's Rachel and Barry.
大家不要一起回头看
No, no, don't everybody look at once.
好 好 现在怎么样
Okay, okay. What's going on?
他们只是在交谈
Okay, they're just talking.
他看起来有没有很生气
Yeah well, does he look upset?
他是不是一副像被告之去死的样子
Does he look like he was just told to shove anything?
没有 他在微笑
No, no, actually he's smiling.
天啊 不要那样
Oh my God. Don't do that.
怎么了怎么了怎么了
What? What? What?
对面有个男人踢了鸽子一脚
That man across the street just kicked that pigeon.
基本上 提案就是这样成为法案的
And basically, that's how a bill becomes a law.
知道了吗 嘿 瑞秋      嘿
See? Hey, Rach.         Hey.
你们还好吧
How'd it go?
说真的 感觉还真好
You know, it was, it was actually really great.
他带我去俄国茶坊吃午餐
He took me to lunch at the Russian Tea Room.
我吃的鸡肉 就是那种
And I had that chicken, you know.
一刺奶油就全流出来了
where you poke it and all the butter squirts out.
今天不是鸟类的好日子
Not a good day for birds.
然后我们去逛百货公司
And then we took a walk down to Bendels.
我跟他说不要
And I told him not to.
但他还是给我买了一小瓶香奈儿香水
But he got me a little bottle of Chanel.
很好
That's nice.
那是在你跟他说之前还是之后
Now was that before or after you told him
让他别再打电话 别再给你送花
to stop calling, stop sending you flowers
不要再烦你
and to generally leave you alone, huh?
那个我们一直没提到
Right. Well, we never actually got to that.
能再见到他的感觉真好
Oh, it was just so nice to see him again, you know?
很舒服很熟悉
It was, it was comfortable and it was familiar.
感觉真好
It was just nice.
感觉真好 你讲两次了
That's, that's "nice" twice.
瑞秋 这到底是怎么回事
Rachel, what's going on?
他不是那个在圣坛前被你甩掉的巴瑞吗
Isn't this the same Barry who you left at the altar?
你上哪儿去了
Where have you been?
是啊 可是今天和他在一起感觉不一样
Yeah, but it was different with him today.
他今天不像个矫正牙医
I mean, he wasn't like Orthodontist Guy, you know?
我们玩得很开心 这有什么不对吗
I mean, we had fun. Is there anything wrong with that?
有
Yes!
为什么      我有我的理由
Why?         I have my reasons.
事实是 他已经订婚了 而未婚妻刚好是
Okay, how about the fact that he's engaged to another woman
你以前最好的朋友 这没关系吗
who just happens to be your ex-best friend?
好啦 好啦 好啦 好啦
All right. All right, all right, all right, all right.
我知道这样做很蠢
I know it's stupid.
我今天下午去找他
I'll go see him this afternoon.
结束这整件事
And I will just put an end to it.
哇 哇      对啊
Wow! Wow!        Yeah.
我没疯吧 以前都不是这样的
I'm not crazy, right? I mean, it was never like that.
你没疯 以前不是这样的
No, it wasn't.
这里有个小水槽真好
Oh. It was so nice having this little sink here.
丹妮儿 我没想到是答录机接的
Oh Danielle, I wasn't expecting the machine.
有空的话 打电话给我
Give me a call when you get a chance.
再见
Bye bye!
天啊
Oh God!
你这两个小时就在忙这个
That's what you've been working on for the past two hours?
喂 我是在演练
Hey, l've been honing.
和盘子有什么关系
What was with the dishes?
我要她以为我在餐厅里
Oh, I wanted her to think I might be in a restaurant.
我也有自己的娱乐生活
You know, I might have some kind of life.
总不能让她觉得 我是在这儿演练了两个小时吧
Like I haven't been sitting around here honing for the last two hours?
快看 又来了
Look look, he's doing it again.
那个拿望远镜的家伙
The guy with the telescope.
我的天啊
Oh my God!
走开 不要再往这边看了
Oh. Go away! Stop looking in here!
好极了 现在他也在跟我们挥手
Great. Now he's waving back.
我们要想个办法对付那个家伙
We gotta do something about that guy.
今天早上 我抓到他在偷窥我们家
This morning, I caught him looking into our apartment.
我吓一跳 感觉像是什么都不能做了
It creeps me out. I feel like I can't do stuff.
你都做些什么
What kind of stuff?
成熟一点好不好 我说的不是那些色情的事
Will you grow up? I'm not talking about sexy stuff.
我只不过是煮饭时全裸而已
but like, when I'm cooking naked.
你煮饭时全裸
You cook naked?
对啊 吐司 麦片粥 不会溅出来的食物
Yeah, toast, oatmeal. Nothing that spatters.
你们看我干嘛 我又不知道
What are you looking at me for? I didn't know that.
怎么了
What's the matter?
我只是 巴瑞 这样不好
Oh, I just... Oh, Barry, this was not good.
不 那感觉非常非常好
No, it was. It was very, very good.
那敏蒂呢      比跟敏蒂好太多了
What about Mindy?         Oh, way better than Mindy.
不是指那个 我是说 你跟敏蒂怎么办
No, not that. I mean, what about you and Mindy?
如果你愿意 我去跟她退婚
Oh. If you want, I'll just break it off with her.
不 不 不 不 不
No no no no no.
不要那样 不要因为我退婚
I mean, don't do that. I mean not for me.
法柏医生 巴比拉什来做调整
Dr. Farber, Bobby Rush is here for his adjustment.
谢谢你 柏妮丝
Thanks, Bernice.
我们这个周末去远一点的地方吧
Let's go away this weekend.
巴瑞 拜托 这太...
Oh, Barry. Come on. This is all way too...
不 不 我们可以去阿鲁巴岛
No,no, we can, we can go to Aruba.
我在本来应该是我们蜜月的时候去过了
When I went there on what would've been our honeymoon
那里真的很美 你会很喜欢的
It was, it was really nice. You would've liked it.
我本来有穿胸罩
I had a bra.
嘿 法柏医生
Hey, Dr. Farber.
好 葛林小姐  一切看起来都很好
All right, Miss Green, everything looks fine.
我想我们已经看到一点进展了
Yep, I think we're starting to see some real progress here.
怎么      我12岁 不代表我很笨
What?         I'm 12, I'm not stupid.
我能不能借用你们的电话      可以
Can I use your phone?         Yeah.
不过 供日后参考
But for future reference.
你手里的那个东西 也可以用来当电话使
That thing in your hand can also be used as a phone.
对呀 线路没问题呀
Yes, it's working.
她为什么不回我电话
Why isn't she calling me back?
她也许根本没听到你的留言
Maybe she never got your message.
你也可以打她的答录机
You know, if you want, you could call her machine.
如果听到很多哔哔声
And if she has a lot of beeps
表示她很有可能还没听留言
that means she probably didn't get her messages yet.
你们不觉得这样会让我看起来有点
You don't think that makes me seem a little...
绝望 饥渴 可悲
Desperate? Needy? Pathetic?
哈 你一定看过我的征友启事
Uha, you obviously saw my personal ad.
哔了几声      她接起来了
How many beeps?         She answered.
这个时候你就可以用 我们讨论过的 "喂"这个字
You see, this is where you'd use that "hello" word we talked about.
我才不要
I'm not gonna talk to her.
很明显她已听到我的留言 选择不回我电话
She obviously got my message and is choosing not to call me.
现在我不但饥渴 还被冷落
Now I'm needy and snubbed.
天呀 我真想念纯饥渴的滋味
God, I miss just being needy.
嘿      嘿
Hey.       Hey.
他的反应如何
So how'd he take it?
其实还蛮不错的
Pretty well, actually.
瑞秋 你的头发上怎么会有牙线
Rach, how come you have dental floss in your hair?
是吗
Oh, do I?
啊哈
Uhhah!
我们在牙医椅上做爱
We ended up having sex in his chair.
你们在牙医椅上做爱
You had sex in his chair?
我说得有点大声 对不对
I said that a little too loudly, didn't I?
你们怎么了?
You, you had what?
在牙医椅上做爱
Sex in his chair.
怎么 你在想什么
What... What were you thinking?
我也不知道 我们都还对对方有感觉
I don't know. I mean we still care about each other.
我们有一段过去 就跟你和卡萝一样
There's a history there. It's like you and Carol.
不 不 不
No. No. no.
跟我和卡萝完全不同
It's nothing like me and Carol.
拜托 如果她跟你说
Please. If she said to you
罗斯 我现在就要你 就在这沙发上
"Ross, I want you on this couch, right here, right now."
你会怎么说
What would you say?
我闪开 可能会有所帮助
If it helps, I could slide over.
那完全是两回事
It's a totally different situation.
这是苹果跟橙子 矫正牙医和女同性恋
It's apples and oranges. It's orthodontists and lesbians.
我要走了
I gotta go.
你要去哪儿
Where are you going?
我就是得走 可以吗
I just have to go, all right?
我走还需要理由吗
Do I need a reason, huh?
我的人生还有别的事要做
I mean, I have things to do with my life.
我的行程排得非常紧
I have a jam packed schedule.
我已经赶得喘不过气来了 可以吗
And I am late for keeping up with it, okay?
喂 喂
Hello? Hello?
喂
Hello?
敏蒂
Huh. Mindy！
嗨 你好
Hi. Hey, how are you?
对 我听说了 恭喜 这真是太好了
Yes, yes, I heard. Congratulations. That is so great.
真的 噢 天啊
Really. Oh God!
好
Okay!
好 我明天要上班
Okay. Well, I'm working tomorrow.
但是如果你愿意 可以过来看看
But if you want, you can come by if you'd like.
好
Okay!
太好了
Great.
好吧
All right!
明天见
So I'll see you tomorrow.
好 再见
Okay. Bye.
天啊 噢 天啊 噢 天啊 噢
Oh God. Oh God. Oh God...
敏蒂还好吗
So how's Mindy?
她明天想见我
Oh, she wants to see me tomorrow.
她的语气听起来很怪 我得打电话给巴端
Oh, she sounded really weird. I gotta call Barry.
喂 是我 我 哈 敏蒂
Hi, it's me. I just... Ha! Mindy.
敏蒂 嗨
Mindy. Hi.
不 我想你应该在那里
No, I figured that's where you'd be.
地狱里充满了你这种人
Hell is filled with people like you.
又来了 偷窥狂又来了
He's back. The peeper's back.
蹲下      蹲下
Get down.         Get down?
然后跳舞
And boogie.
谢谢 我得去上班
Thanks, but I gotta go to work.
顺便让敏蒂把我的眼睛挖出来
And get my eyes scratched out by Mindy.
放心 她也许根本不知道
Relax. Y'know, she may not even know.
拜托 我七个月没跟她联络
Please I haven't heard from her in seven months.
她突然打电话给我
And now she calls me.
还能因为什么事
I mean, what else is it about?
她曾经是我最好的朋友
She was my best friend, you guys.
我们一起去夏令营
We went to camp together.
她教我如何接吻      是吗
She taught me how to kiss.         Yeah?
现在 我成了第三者
Now, you know, I'm like, I'm like the other woman.
我觉得好      有情趣
I feel so...        Naughty.
晚点见
All right, I'll see you guys later.
我送你出去
Oh, hold up. I'll walk out with you.
她教你接吻的时候 你们在夏令营
Now Rach, when she taught you to kiss, you were at camp.
穿的是紧身制服 还是
And were you wearing any kind of little uniform or...
算了
That's fine, yeah.
好 我要去上厕所 你能不能帮我看着电话
Okay, I'm gonna go the bathroom. Will you watch my phone?
你为什么不把电话拿进去
Why don't you just take it with you?
嘿 我们还没进展到第二次约会
Hey, we haven't been on a second date.
她需要听我嘘嘘吗
She needs to hear me pee?
你为什么不干脆打给她
Why don't you just call her?
我不能打给她 我已经留言了 我也是有尊严的
I can't call her. I left a message. I have some pride.
有吗     没有
Do you?         No.
丹妮儿 你好
Danielle, hi!
我是钱德
Hi, it's Chandler.
我很好
I'm fine.
是这样的 不知道你有没有打电话给我
Listen, I don't know if you tried to call me.
因为我很白痴
Because idiot that I am.
不小心把电话关掉了
I accidentally shut off my phone.
哦 好 没问题 好极了 好
Oh, okay. That's fine. That's great. Okay.
她在另一线上讲电话 她再打回来
She's on the other line. She's gonna call me back.
你不是想去嘘嘘吗      所以我才在跳呀
Don't you have to pee?         That's why I'm dancing.
敏蒂      嘿 你好
Mindy.         Hey, you.
嘿 你好
Hey, you.
最近还好吗
So, what's up?
我们应该坐下来说
We should really be sitting for this.
我们当然要坐下
Sure we should.
那么
So...
我知道 最近事情感觉怪怪的
Now, I know things have been weird lately.
但是你是我认识最久的朋友
But you're my oldest friend in the world.
除了萝莉莎菲 我现在不跟她说话了
Except for, maybe Laurie Schaefer who I don't talk to anymore.
自从减肥后 她就一副全世界都欠她的样子
Because she's all bitter now that she lost the weight.
原因是她根本没有一张漂亮的脸
And it turns out she doesn't have a pretty face.
好了 我只问一次
Okay, I'm just gonna ask this once.
而且我要很诚实的答案
And I want a straight answer.
好
Okay.
你愿不愿意当我的伴娘
Will you be my maid of honor?
当然罗      那就太好了
Of course!         Oh, that's so great!
太好了 太好了
It is! It is!
你就只想问这件事吗      对啊
Is that all you wanted to ask me?         That's all.
怎么了 怎么了
What? What?
不只是这件事
That's not all.
一定只有这件事      不 不只
Oh sure, it is.         Oh no, it isn't. No.
我觉得巴瑞在跟别人约会
I think Barry's seeing someone in the city.
你怎么会有这种想法
What would make you think that?
自从我们宣布订婚后
Well, ever since we announced the engagement
他就怪怪的
he's been acting really weird.
昨晚他回家的时候 身上有香奈儿的香水味
And then last night, he came home smelling like Chanel.
真的吗
Really?
敏蒂 如果这样讲 你会好过一点
Mindy, if it'll make you feel any better.
巴瑞跟我订婚后
When Barry and I first got engaged
他的行为也很诡异
he went through a whole weird thing too.
噢 天啊 我就是怕这一点
Oh God. You see, that's what I was afraid of.
怎么了 你是怕哪一点
What? What's were you afraid of?
好吧 好吧
Okay, okay.
巴瑞跟你订婚后
When Barry was engaged to you
他跟我也发展出一点什么
He and I kind of had a little thing on the side.
什么      我知道 我知道
What?         I know. I know.
他跟我求婚时 大家都告诉我
When he proposed to me, everyone said,
不要接受 他以前怎么对瑞秋
"Don't do it. He's gonna do to you
现在也会那么对你
what he did to Rachel."
现在我自己觉得好傻
And now I feel so stupid.
嗯哈
Hmmhuh!
噢 敏蒂
Hmm. Oh, Mindy.
噢 你真的好傻
Oh, you are so stupid.
噢 我们都好傻
Oh, we are both so stupid.
什么意思
What do you mean?
很熟悉的味道吧      噢 不会吧
Smell familiar?        Oh, no.
我很抱歉
Oh, I'm so sorry.
噢 不 是我很抱歉
Oh, no, me. I am so sorry.
不 是我很抱歉 对不起
No, I am sorry. I'm sorry.
老天
Oh my!
一个字 发出声音
Four letters, circle or hoop.
响啊 该死 响
Ring, damn it, ring.
谢谢
Thanks.
嘿 你知道我们的电话坏掉了吗
Hey, you know our phone's not working?
什么
What?
我从咖啡厅打电话给你
I tried to call you from the coffee shop.
一直没有人接
There was no answer.
我把电话关掉了
I turned it off.
我的天啊 我把电话关掉了
Mother of God, I turned it off.
就像你跟她讲的那样
Just like you told her you did.
我只是指出反讽之处
Just pointing out the irony.
我去跟对面的门房谈过了
So listen, I went across the street and talked to the doorman.
知道了偷窥狂的名字 电话可以用了吧
I got the peeper's name. Can I use the phone?
能不能借用你的电话
Can I use your phone?
对 请给我 辛尼马克斯的电话号码
Yeah, the number for a Sidney Marks, please.
暖气设备
"Heating device.'
散热器
Radiator.
两个字
Five letters.
热器
"Rdtor."
辛尼在吗
Yeah, is Sidney there?
哦 你就是
Oh, this is?
辛尼是个女人      辛尼是个女人 那又怎样
Sidney's a woman.         So she's a woman, so what?
对 对 那又怎样
Yeah, yeah, so what?
我住在你对面
Look, I live across the street.
我知道你喜欢用望远镜偷窥
And I know all about you and your little telescope.
我很不高兴 知道吗
And I don't appreciate it, okay?
对 我现在就可以看到你 喂
Yeah! I can see you right now. Hello?
如果我只穿着内裤 在我家走来走去
Look, if I wanna walk around my apartment in my underwear
我没有必要觉得 谢谢
I shouldn't have to feel like... Thank you.
那不是重点
That's not really the point.
重点是 主要是重量训练 但是偶尔
The point is that... Mostly free weights, but occasionally...
乔伊
Joey.
对 我的邻居 没错 褐发的那个
Yeah, my neighbor. Yeah, the brunette.
她说你那天 穿那件绿裙子的时候很漂亮
She said you looked pretty the other day in the green dress.
绿裙子 真的吗
The green dress? Really?
她说那天你很像英格丽保曼
She said you looked like Ingrid Bergman that day.
哪有
No.
嘿      嘿
Hey.         Hey.
有空吗      当然 当然
You got a second?         Sure. sure.
快请
Come on...
进
in?
你好 亲爱的
Hello, sweetheart.
你们两个来这里干嘛
What're'you... What're'you guys doing here?
我们俩来甩了你
We are here to break up with you.
你们俩
Both of you?
我们觉得你是个大烂人
Basically, we think you're a horrible human being.
你该遭到天打雷劈
And bad things should happen to you.
对不起 对不起 天啊 真对不起
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. God, I am so sorry.
我是大白痴 我很软弱 无法控制自己
I'm an idiot. I was weak. I couldn't help myself.
不管我做了什么 我这所以做都是因为我太爱你了
Whatever I did, I only did because I love you so much.
你是在跟哪一个讲 巴瑞
Which one of us are you talking to there, Bar?
敏蒂
Mindy.
敏蒂 当然是敏蒂  一直都是敏蒂
Mindy, of course, Mindy. It was always Mindy.
甚至包括我们在那张椅子上做爱的时候吗
Even when we were having sex in that chair?
我发誓 不管我在做什么
I swear, look, whatever I was doing
心里想的都是你
I was always thinking of you.
拜托哦
Oh, please.
第二次的时候
During that second time,
你根本没法把她从一行人里面挑出来
you couldn't have picked her out of a lineup.
你们还做了两次
You did it twice?
第一次不能算数
Well, the first time didn't really count.
你了解巴瑞的
You know, it was Barry.
噢 对哦
Oh, right.
甜心 宝贝 亲爱的
Honey, baby, sweetheart, look...
再给我一次机会 好不好
Just give me another chance, okay?
我们重新来过 我们再去阿鲁巴岛
We'll start all over again. We'll go back to Aruba.
你怎么说
What do you say?
法柏医生 有点紧急状况需要你处理
Dr. Farber, we've got an emergency here.
杰森卡斯达拉诺 被自己的牙套噎到了
Jason Castalano's choking on his retainer.
天啊 我 马上过去 柏妮丝
Oh, God. I'll be right there, Bernice.
真的 请不要离开 好吗
Look, please, please don't go anywhere, okay?
我马上回来      好
I'll be right back.         Okay.
好 我们会留在这儿 继续恨你
Okay, and we'll be here, hating you.
有没有看到 他走出去的时候 满身大汗
Did you see how he was sweating when he walked out of here?
如果我控制住了他
Listen honey, if I'm hogging the ball too much
你也别客气 过来揍他两拳
you just jump right in there and take a couple of punches.
那感觉肯定超爽
Because I'm telling you, this feels great.
没错 我很确定我还是会嫁给他
Yeah, I'm pretty sure I'm still gonna marry him.
你在说什么啊
What are you talking about?
敏蒂 那家伙是个恶魔
Mindy, the guy is the devil.
他是披着人皮的撒旦
He is Satan in a smock.
我知道他不完美
Look, I know he's not perfect.
但是 到头来
But the truth is, at the end of the day
我还是想当 牙科博士 巴瑞法柏医生的太太
I still really wanna be Mrs. Dr. Barry Farber, D.D.S.
噢 天啊
Oh, God.
我希望你还是能够为我高兴
I hope you can find some way to be happy for me.
也希望你仍然愿意当我的伴娘
And I hope you'll still be my maid of honor.
我希望巴瑞不会在阿鲁巴岛 把你生吞活剥吃掉
And I hope Barry doesn't kill you and eat you in Aruba.
你还好吗
You okay?
还好
Yeah.
真的
Really?
Yeah.
你知道吗 自从我在婚礼上甩了巴瑞跑掉后
You know, ever since I ran out on Barry at the wedding
我一直想知道 我的决定是否正确
I have wondered whether I made the right choice.
现在我知道了
Oh, and now I know.
很为你高兴
I'm so glad.
大日子唷
Big day.
好 我可以赞成
All right, I'll give you this.
花生先生比较会穿衣服
Mr. Peanut is a better dresser.
他戴着单片眼镜 加上礼帽
I mean, he's got the monocle, he's got the top hat.
你们知道他是同性恋吗
Did you know he's gay?
只是想搞清楚 你是在公布花生先生出柜的消息吗
I just wanna clarify this. Are you outing Mr. Peanut?
钱德      丹妮儿 你好
Chandler?         Danielle! Hi!
各位 这位是丹妮儿 丹妮儿 这都是我朋友
Everybody, this is Danielle. Danielle, everybody.
你好      你好
Hi.        Hi.
你怎么会在这里
What are you doing here?
我一直打电话给你
Well, I've been calling you.
后来才知道电话号码错了
But it turns out I had your number wrong.
我从查号台拿到正确号码后
And when I finally got the right one from Information
却没人接
there was no answer.
我就想来这里
So, I thought I'd just come down here.
看看你好不好
And make sure you were okay.
噢 我很好
Oh, I'm okay.
改天我们出去逛逛好吗
Listen, maybe we could get together later?
很好
That sounds good.
我打给你或是你打给我 都可以
I'll call your or you call me, whatever, you know.
当然      好
You got it.        Okay.
各位 再见      再见
Bye, everybody.        Bye.
哇哦      好啊 就是要这样
Woohoo!        Yeah, there you go.
第二次约会
Second date.
我不确定
I don't know.
你不确定
You don't know?
她看起来很讨人喜欢
Oh, she seems nice and everything.
但是大老远跑来这里
But that whole thing about her coming all the way down here
只为了看我好不好
just to see if I was okay?
有人那么黏人的吗
I mean, how needy is that?
【海盗美剧 友情制作】
-== http://www.hdmeiju.com ==-
新浪微博：@海盗美剧
海盗编号：HDT20-P1-24-20-01-1212